Our primary objective this
time around was to find you,
Boxxo, and I'm so glad we did.
We could head back but I have a proposal.
There's something that might
be worth sticking around
the Labyrinth Stratum a bit
longer for if you're game.
If I'm game?
Now, this mission came as a humble
request from the Menagerie of Fools.
They want our help in defeating
the Skeletitan of Stratumlord.
He's the one we ran into before.
We weren't considering
defeating it originally.
But it does present a danger
to hunters if left unchecked.
So, bearing that in mind, I for one feel
it's my duty to help them if possible.
Director Bear is a consummate leader.
I imagine it'd be prudent to let the
Menagerie make their case as well.
He said it, but I like explaining things.
Yeah, we want to defeat
this Stratumlord guy.
And we think that with your help,
we've got a fighting chance.
But, like, have you met the guy?
Look, I get that it's
a big-time undertaking.
But since I love explaining,
I'll tell you this too.
Every member of the Menagerie
of Fools has a personal goal.
We're resolute about achieving
these goals, no matter the cost.
Even if that means people
treat us like fools,
calling us a menagerie as
if we're a bunch of animals.
Tell me something, Boxo.
Have you heard the
legend of the labyrinth?
Too bad.
It holds that anyone who reaches the
dungeon, the labyrinth's lowest level,
and manages to meet its requirements,
will be granted any wish they make.
That sounds pretty awesome.
Hmm.
Thank you
so
much for watching.
Thank you.
I'm proud of you,
People may have reached the lowest level,
but to this day, no one has
conquered the dungeon yet.
No one knows what the requirements are.
That's what we're after, Boxo.
Thanks for letting me explain.
Requirements, huh?
Rumor is there's not so little
catch about those wishes.
Seems they can only be granted
if you have one of those
coins that drops when you
take down a Stratum Lord.
Wait a sec.
Like the eight-legged crocodile
coin I have in my inventory?
Who knew it was worth all that?
You know that the Menagerie of
Fools consists of eight members.
The twins have the same wish.
The vice captain and I also share
one, so that makes six wishes total.
We've already got three
of those coins between us.
Half of what we need.
So I could use my coin to
have a wish granted too?
Maybe I should become a super
high-performance vending machine.
Or not, I don't know.
And according to Hulemy,
you've got a human soul buried
somewhere in that Boxxo body of yours.
If you work with us,
I don't see any reason you couldn't
put that soul back into a human body.
Huh? For real?
Don't tease, you mean it?
Yeah, I remember stumbling across a situation
like that in a book once upon a time.
So, Boxxo in human form, huh?
You could even win a reward!
Appreciate the save there, Boxxo.
Regardless, we gotta get to the lowest
level before we'll get any wishes.
So, to beef up our abilities,
we're hitting all the strata, keeping
ears to the ground for news about lords,
finding them, and taking them out.
Which brings me to this.
When you defeated the
eight-legged crocodile,
did one of those coins I mentioned appear?
Hello there!
I see.
And do you have it on you right now?
Hello there!
I'll be.
Best news I've heard in a while.
Suboxo Lamas, you're officially
invited to join the Menagerie.
I mean, you don't have to sign
on for every quest or anything.
But you're welcome to work with us on
campaigns when we need some extra help.
I'm in, but what about Lamas?
Hmm, sounds like a plan.
Then we could talk for real.
And you could even try my cooking, too.
Fine, twist my arm.
I'll work with you, too.
Glad to hear it.
So, Boxo, what do you say?
Want to join this ship of fools?
Hello there.
Heck yes, Boxo.
This is the best day ever.
And with Boxo along for the ride, we'll
never have to worry about food, either.
The thought of campaigning
just got a whole lot better.
Back to being human? Huh.
If I had a human body, I could
probably feel their warmth.
That would be nice.
Well, don't you all look
prepped and ready to go?
How about we get our bearings, shall we?
No pun intended.
That's the new map?
I couldn't call that
accurate even to be polite.
If only I could share my security
camera images with him somehow.
Oh, I could use this function.
Show up.
Is that...
Yes, the labyrinth stratum.
Boxo, how'd you get this?
Interesting.
Boxxo, are you somehow able to
show us all the things you've seen?
Hello there!
That's quite an impressive feat, Boxxo.
Guess who's getting a bonus
from the Hunters Association?
Demon, please.
Coming right up.
I hope this makes the
approach a little easier.
Now, how to defeat the Stratum
Lord, the Flame Skelet Titan?
Just up ahead of us, there's a rather
sizable trap waiting to be sprung,
but it only activates under very
specific conditions. Let me guess.
Those are weight-related.
That's right.
Anything above a certain weight
will trigger the trap's door,
which opens to a cavernous
hole in the ground.
We once tried to march a large group through
this stratum and paid the price for it.
As you might have surmised, we'll drop
the Flameskeletitan into that hole.
A hole big enough for
that thing to fit into?
Cavernous indeed.
How exactly do you plan to get a stratum,
Lord, to fall for a
trap in its own stratum?
We'll use its expertise against it.
If the Skeletitan won't
activate the trap on its own,
we'll just have to do it manually.
I guess that's why we put this campaign
group together with quality over quantity,
Amai.
Aha!
Now I understand why
Karyos and Gorth are here.
These two are a lot more
skilled than your average guard.
Alright, everyone, stay
close to the left-hand wall.
By close, I mean backs up against it.
Look closely now.
Make sure you take in the
exact placement of the hole.
Right, time for my favorite
thing, a detail of explanation.
The hole is over twice as deep
as the flame skeleton is tall.
We plan to lure it to right on top
of the hole and let it fall in.
But even if that works, we doubt
it'll be enough to finish it off.
Okay, so then what?
Are we gonna attack it from up here?
Of course. Thing is,
even if we attack from above,
the fire all over its body will
melt everything we throw at it.
That's why I'm thinking we could make
use of the Vice Captain's water magic,
combined with some water from Box Hill.
Fill the hole before we dump
the big fiery guy in. I see.
So the plan is to extinguish the flames,
exposing the bone like we
would with flame skulls,
and then inflict as
much damage as possible.
Voxo,
is it even possible to
sell or dispense enough
water to implement the
plan we're proposing?
I can dispense bottled water, but it'll
take days to dispense enough to do that.
Dang it!
A vending machine's sole purpose
is to provide for its customers!
I'll add a function.
Well, that's yet another shape
I've never seen Boxo make before.
So, I take it we can interpret
this change as your answer, Boxo?
Hello there!
So there are multiple extensions now,
which leads me to believe each of them
serves a different function when you push it?
much like punching in different
numbers to buy different items.
There are some pictures here.
Maybe they tell you how to use it.
Let's see.
Squeeze this lever and it will
dispense water. Hello there.
Please insert coins.
You're up, Vice Captain.
Thank you, Captain.
I so enjoy you ordering me to pay for
things when you never open your own purse.
Okay, folks, ready for blast-off.
Whoa!
This is great!
That could easily extinguish
a flame skull, no problem.
With that rate of flow, filling the
hole will take days, but it'll work.
You're a lifesaver, Boxo.
Sure, but there's just one little problem.
I can change forms.
but I can only maintain the
new one for two hours a day.
What a pain.
It's been two days since then.
For just one hour each day, I turn
into a power washer and spray water.
At other times, I have them
throw in bottled water.
Once it's been thrown, I do
away with all the bottles.
Things like huge hog fiends and flame
skulls have shown up several times,
but they're no threat for a
group of this skill level.
When flame skulls appear,
Llamas puts me on her back
and Shui gleefully douses
the fiery foes with the
sprayer to take them out.
Right, time to find out
how much water's collected.
Keep a firm grip on the lifeline, okay?
Wow, didn't expect it to be as
cold as midwinter down here.
Looks like this ground drains
better than we anticipated.
It hasn't collected at
all. I see. Now what?
It was a good plan, but we're
going to have to modify.
Dropping it in the pit should still
work, but as for the rest of the plan,
it needs massaging.
Good drainage, you say?
I've got this.
Boxo?
Wait, does this mean you've got an idea?
Hey now, I see where you're headed.
Since it's so cold down there, we can
fill it with ice instead of water.
My speed has increased, so I'm able
to produce the ice cubes much faster.
But I don't know, I'm skeptical.
Is an ice water bath going to be
enough to defeat the stratum horde?
Hey, Boxo, what you thinking about?
Something I can help you with? Huh?
How can you tell?
I don't know if you've noticed
or not, but when you're thinking,
your lighting flickers a little.
Wow, it does?
Voxo, can I ask you something?
Hello there!
Do you even actually
want to be human again?
Anyone else would think that's
a no-brainer, but not Lamas.
She knows me too well.
At first, I did want that.
I guess I would enjoy being able to
have real conversations with her.
But still, a scary thought haunts me.
If I weren't a vending machine,
would my friends still value me?
What would I be worth to them?
Right now, my sense of value is clear
because of all I can do for them.
But if I went back to being human...
Boxo?
Don't get me wrong, I'm sure
they'd be happy at first.
But once they saw what they'd
lost by my transformation,
they might start wishing I was
still a magic vending machine.
Not gonna lie, thoughts
like that terrify me.
That's why I can't bring myself
to acquire the telepathy function,
no matter how it might help.
How pathetic is that?
What sad sack soul has more confidence
as a vending machine than a human?
Hello there. Too bad.
Hmm?
Does that mean that you're not sure?
Times like these make me wish we could
talk about all kinds of things, you know?
Oh, and like I said before, I
really want you to try my cooking.
She's right.
I will be human again, and Lamas
and I will walk hand in hand.
Maybe that alone is enough.
Several more days went by.
The pits collected quite a bit of ice,
so it's finally time to
put the plan into motion.
Boxo, how do you think
things look, honestly?
Does the plan have a chance of success?
Hello there!
You seem pretty confident.
The Flame Skeletiton's fire
can vaporize water instantly.
I just wonder if ice
is going to be enough.
You could even win a reward!
Do it, McTenay! Now! Yes, sir!
The reaction will release a
rush of steam, so watch out!
Huh?
The water should have vaporized by now.
What's happening?
Hang on!
The skeleton's fire! It went out!
I don't know what went down,
but if the fire's out, it's out.
Time to start throwing!
The flames were extinguished,
but there's no steam?
I'm the only one who knows why.
What I was chucking into
the hole wasn't ice at all.
It was dry ice, and dry ice is
essentially solidified carbon dioxide.
So when the flame's skeleton fell in,
the hole filled with carbon dioxide gas.
Fire can't burn without oxygen!
and carbon dioxide collects at the bottom?
since it's heavier than oxygen.
In other words, it put out the flames.
It's a good thing my plan worked, because
if it had failed, we'd have been screwed.
Mikenne, how's it look down there?
It looks like it's taking
a fair amount of damage,
but we're gonna need to hit harder!
if we want this to be over anytime soon.
I wonder how we could hit it harder.
It'd take something big and heavy.
Something sturdy.
Huh?
Boxo would make the perfect
weapon in this case.
But if it doesn't work, he might
break or even be totally destroyed.
He was fine after falling
through a stratum split.
That was worse than this. Uh,
can you guys stop talking
about doing something
so dangerous with me
like I'm not right here?
Not happening!
We can't force Boxo into danger!
Especially since there's
a chance it won't work.
So I vote no, too.
Yeah, you're right.
and it'd be cruel to put
any further burden on them.
Shall we jump in and rush the thing?
With the flames
extinguished, we could win.
The pit is full of carbon dioxide gas.
Go down there and you
won't have enough oxygen.
You will all die of
carbon dioxide poisoning.
Oh, seems Boxo agrees.
I don't!
But we have to do something.
The Flame Skeletiton's trying
to climb out of the hole!
Look, we can't afford to
miss this opportunity.
Are you guys ready to win this?
This is bad.
If I don't act fast, my
friends could all die.
There has to be some way to stop them.
I know!
Huh?
Boxo, why are you changing forms again?
Hello there.
Please insert coins.
Hey, stop that, Boxo!
Nobody needs stuff like that right now!
Don't be a pervert, jeez!
Oh no, I messed up!
Thank you very much!
Help!
Watch out!
12 damage.
Durability has been decreased by 12.
Looks like I managed to finish it off.
That means everything's okay.
Boxo!
That was so reckless!
Hold on a minute!
I'm coming down to get you!
Too bad.
Too bad. Too bad.
Boxo!
Are you trying to tell us it's
still dangerous down there?
Hello there!
There!
Flame's Skeletitan coin was
added to my list of possessions.
Oh, Mickey, shut the hole, quickly.
You got it.
Boxo! Huh?
What would we have done
if you had broken, huh?
You could even win a reward.
Don't give me that.
I gotta say, I'm mad at you, Boxo.
Come on, cut the guy
a little slack, Lamas.
No sense punishing a friend for a good
deed, unless you want him to be mad at you.
But I...
Fine, I'll drop it.
I'm just mad because I care.
No more crazy stunts like that, Kay.
I didn't answer yes or no.
If it meant saving everyone,
I'd do it again and again.
And I didn't want to make a promise I
couldn't keep, especially not to Lamas.
And then, she smiled an
exasperated smile at me.
You guys done talking
because I have an important
question for you tell me
did the stratum lord's coin
happen to drop while you
were down in that hole hello
there oh you even picked it
up for me how kind hold on
what's the big idea hula
me you're trying to claim
the reward like there's no
question that it's yours but
boxo defeated the flame
skeleton which means you're
not the rightful owner of
this coin sorry guess you're
right about that it'd be
wrong to deny that everything
worked out because of your
exploits box so you were
in this coin fair and square
with your heroics and I
would never take that right
from you so how about this
let me buy it off you how
does a hundred gold coin
sound did he say a hundred
gold coins converted into
points that's a hundred
thousand heck yes you can't
hmm that's about the going
right for stratum lord coin?
so I can vouch that he's
offering you a square deal.
You heard him, Boxo. What'll it be?
Not only is that fair and square,
it's an embarrassment of riches.
Plus, I already have one Stratum Lord
coin, so I don't need another one.
Hello there.
I knew you'd agree, Boxo, but I'm
glad you didn't waste any time.
You mind if I pay you another day?
I'm a little bit cash poor at the moment.
Well done, everyone.
Let's head for home.
Alright, now for the journey back
to the Clear Flow Lake Stratum.
Looks like all I'll get
to see at the Labyrinth
Stratum is the view from the
sky in these main avenues.
Yeah, I probably won't
see this place again.
I'll
see you
next time.
I don't know, but this moment I'm happy.
Today is a good day.
I'm always hungry.
much.
I look forward to serving you again.